http://www.sk.lung.ca/about-us/website-policies/privacy-policy

Jump to content
Saskatchewan
Lung HealthAir QualityAsbestos AwarenessLung Health CheckKeep Your Lungs HealthyCannabisRadonTobaccoScentsSchool ZoneVapingLung DiseasesAsthmaCOVID-19COPDFluLung CancerPneumoniaPulmonary FibrosisSleep ApneaLung TestsTuberculosisDiseases A - ZOrgan DonationMedicationsInhalersLung ResearchFunding OpportunitiesResearch We SupportParticipate in ResearchSaskatchewan ResearchersSupport ResearchHealthcare ProvidersCOVID-19 ResourcesFall Webinar Series 2020Inspired Breathing Conference 2021Home Oxygen TestersProfessional SocietiesResourcesRESPTRECSupport & EducationBREATHE AmbassadorsCaring Breaths Financial Assistance ProgramCertified Educators in SaskatchewanFind an Asthma or COPD EducatorFind a Lung Health ProgramLung Health MaterialsLung HelplineNewslettersSupport GroupsGet InvolvedBreathing As OneDonateMonthly GivingFun Ways To Support Our MissionLeave a LegacyMembershipCommunity PartnershipsVolunteerTell us your story
About UsWhat We DoWho We AreAnnual Reports and Financial StatementsContact UsWebsite PoliciesEmploymentNews RoomSearchContact UsNews
You are hereHome › About Us › Website Policies › Privacy PolicyPrint PageText resize decrease -A Text resize reset A Text resize increase +A
Due to the increase in COVID-19 cases, our office is closed until further notice. Please see our news post for more information.
Privacy Policy
Return to About Us
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Disclaimer
Copyright Notice
Protecting your privacy is important to The Lung Association of Saskatchewan. The following policy provides information on how The Lung Association of Saskatchewan collects, uses, and safeguards the personal information you provide on our web site. This policy may change from time to time. Please reread this policy periodically.
Information collection
When you browse the Lung Association of Saskatchewan web site, you do so anonymously. We do not collect personal information, including your e-mail address. The Lung Association of Saskatchewan is a member of the Canadian Centre for Philanthropy, and the Association of Fundraising Professionals. We adhere to the privacy guidelines of these organizations.
At times we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, such as your e-mail address and postal address, for purposes such as corresponding with us, registering at our site, making a donation, entering a contest, or participating in an online survey. However, when at all possible, an option to remain anonymous will be provided to those who wish to preserve their right to anonymity.
For reasons of security, credit card information is not stored on the web server. We will retain your order information for our records, but this information is never shared with unaffiliated third parties. You are welcome to read our security statement for further information about credit card and server security.
Information use
When you supply the Lung Association of Saskatchewan with your personal information we may use it:
to guide the development of new features and services relevant to web users
to contact you by e-mail or direct mail about future events or promotions offered by the Lung Association of Saskatchewan
to provide further information related to the issue around which you supplied your personal information
The Lung Association of Saskatchewan may exchange donor's contact information with reputable charities. This cost-effective method helps encourage support from new donors. If you do not want your name to be exchanged email us at: lists@sk.lung.ca to opt out.
The Lung Association of Saskatchewan's web site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We have physical and electronic barriers that ensure that all personal information is fully encrypted during all transactions. Please note, however, that no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. As a result, while we attempt to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us and you transmit such information to us at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission we attempt in every way to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems.
The Lung Association of Saskatchewan recognizes the importance of privacy and security regarding the information you send us over the Internet. Security is a priority and we have devoted a significant effort to ensure that our online security measures help to safeguard your information.
Security
The Lung Association of Saskatchewan takes your privacy and security seriously. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information you provide to us online.
All secure transactions are processed on our secure server, using the latest TLS/SSL technologies and we use iATS Payments to process credit cards. To help protect yourself, always ensure that you are running the latest version of your web browser and that the security features are enabled.
Comments and enquiries should be e-mailed to webmaster@sk.lung.ca or by calling (306) 343-9511.
Disclaimer
Page Last Updated: 04/08/2018
